{
    "id": "62ad9364bfcc4e9fa94c25acf43384dc",
    "title": "Money Idioms",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "4714e65b42294b54b6782807a96de3cf",
            "title": "Money Idioms",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "If these activists are really interested in eradicating poverty and malnutrition they must put their money where their …………………… is.",
                    "description": "To put your money where your mouth is to practice what you preach.",
                    "answers": [
                        "hand",
                        "mouth",
                        "heart"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He can buy just about anything he wants. His wife has got ……………………… of money.",
                    "description": "Pots of money = lot of money",
                    "answers": [
                        "pots",
                        "tins",
                        "barrels"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He doesn’t have to work. He’s already got plenty of money to ……………………… around.",
                    "description": "To throw money around is to spend it carelessly on unnecessary things.",
                    "answers": [
                        "kick",
                        "fool",
                        "throw"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "They hit pay ……………………………. with their new gaming app.",
                    "description": "Hit pay dirt = Find something very profitable ",
                    "answers": [
                        "dirt",
                        "packet",
                        "smart"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I had to pay through the ………………………… to get my old car repaired.",
                    "description": "To pay through the nose is to pay too much money for something.",
                    "answers": [
                        "ears",
                        "eyes",
                        "nose"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Employers are paying ………………………. dollar to retain talent.",
                    "description": "To pay top dollar is to pay a lot of money for something.",
                    "answers": [
                        "high",
                        "big",
                        "top"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "That velvet gown cost me a …………………………..",
                    "description": "When something costs you a pretty penny, it is very expensive.",
                    "answers": [
                        "pretty penny",
                        "handsome penny",
                        "hot penny"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She may be .......................................... poor, but she is honest.",
                    "description": "Dirt poor = Extremely poor",
                    "answers": [
                        "dirt",
                        "filth"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She may be as poor as a …………………………….., but she is content.",
                    "description": "As poor as church mice = Very poor ",
                    "answers": [
                        "church mouse",
                        "alley cat",
                        "street dog"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He earns the money, but it is his wife who holds the ..............................................",
                    "description": "To hold the purse strings = To hold the purse strings is to control a family’s or company’s money",
                    "answers": [
                        "purse strings",
                        "wallet",
                        "coffers"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is ............................................ rich and that’s why he married her.",
                    "description": "Filthy rich = Extremely rich",
                    "answers": [
                        "dirt",
                        "dirty",
                        "filthy"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You can’t ...................................... Peter to pay Paul. If that is your policy you will never be out of debt.",
                    "description": "Rob Peter to pay Paul = Borrow money from one person to pay back money borrowed from another person.",
                    "answers": [
                        "rob",
                        "kidnap",
                        "pawn"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}